Guide to the University of Chicago, Yerkes Observatory, Office of the Director Records 1891-1946
University of Chicago Library
- Series II: 1903-1946
  - C, 1932, Calculating Machine (S. W. Allen Company), 1 page Calvert, Mary, 5 pages Cambridge Instrument Company, 10 pages Cannon, Annie J., 1 page Cap, Leon, 4 pages Capp, H. E., 2 pages Carpenter, A. H., 3 pages Carpenter, Mrs. Hubbard, 1 page Carr, F. E., 1 page Cattell, J. M. (American Men of Science), 4 pages Central Scientific, 1 page Chabot Observatory, 1 page Chaos Club, 2 pages Cherrington, Ernest (Perkins), 2 pages Chicago American, 3 pages Chicago Herald and Examiner, 1 page Chicago Tribune, 4 pages Childs, C. R., 1 page Christmas cards, 2 pages Church, L. C. (Walworth Lumber), 3 pages Ciel et Terre, 1 page Claremont Aero Service, 2 pages Cleveland Baptist Association (D. R. Sharpe), 1 page Coles, William G., 2 pages Colliers Magazine, 2 pages Columbia University Library, 12 pages Commander Hotel, Cambridge Massachusetts, 1 page Committee for Relief in Belgium (P. C. Galpin), 7 pages F. E. Compton Company, 2 pages Comrie, L. J., 1 page Conklin, Jean, 2 pages Conservation Committee, Wisconsin, 5 pages Cory, Ralph, 1 page Coursen, C. Blair, 3 pages G. Cramer Dry Plate, 5 pages Crisler, Bonnie, 2 pages Crite, Oliver, 2 pages Criterion Plays, 2 pages Crow, Marguerite O’L., 2 pages Crucible Steel Casting Company, 1 page Crump, Clifford, 3 pages Curtis, H. D., 4 pages Customs Service, Milwaukee, 4 pages Customs Service, New York, 1 page (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - A-D, 1932, Applications for positions: M. Benson, C. E. Bisdee, S. P. Choate, G. C. Claude, L. W. Hartel, M. A. Hawes, P. Hayford, F. C. Hernoteau, J. H. Hett, F. H. Johnson, E. Kerchmar, M. Long, H. Maager, L. Moore, L. R. Newton, V. Peterson, J. Shobat (for Kostitzin), S. L. Thorndike, W. F. Uplinger, C. M. Wolf, Jr., L. A. Ware American Astronomical Society, 2 pages Bank Deposits Daily News (Chicago), 1 page Daily Times (Chicago), 1 page Danforth, M., 2 pages William Dawson and Sons, 1 page W. P. Day, 2 pages Dempster, A. J., 2 pages Dexter, W. C., 2 pages Eugene Dietzgen Company, 4 pages Dimler, F. J., 2 pages Dingle, Herbert, 3 pages Dobbin, Leonard, 1 page Dominion Astrophysical Observatory, 5 pages Douglas, A. V. (McGill), 2 pages Draft, H., 1 page Dugan, Raymond S. (Princeton, American Astronomical Society Secretary), 11 pages Duncan, John C., 2 pages Dunham, Theodore, Jr. (Mount Wilson), 4 pages Dyer, H. J., 2 pages Dyson, Frank (Greenwich), 1 page (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - E, 1932, Eastman Kodak, 31 pages Observatorio Ebro (L. Rodes), 1 page Emanuelli, P. (Vatican), 2 pages Solar Eclipse Expedition of August 31, 1932, 7 photos and 51 items (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - F-G, 1932, Farnsworth, Alice, 2 pages Farnsworth, Golderia, 2 pages F. W. Fecker Company, 12 pages Field Museum, 2 pages First National Bank, 1 page Fish-Schurman Company, 1 page Fisher, Clyde (American Museum), 4 pages Fletcher, A., 1 page Fletcher, L., 2 pages Foote, H. M., 2 pages Forsythe, W. E. (GE), 4 pages Fox, Philip (Adler, Chicago Astronomical Society), 39 pages Franklin Institute, 3 pages Gaertner Scientific Corporation, 17 pages Gale, Henry G., 2 pages Garrett, W. H., 3 pages Genard, L. (Liege), 3 pages General Electric Company, 1 page Geneva Foundry, 2 pages G. Gennert, Incorporated, 6 pages Geological Survey, Department of Interior, 1 page Gilles, J., 2 pages Gingrich, C., 2 pages Gladden, Sanford C., 2 pages Glenn, Sylvia, 1 page C. P. Goatz, 1 page Graybar Electric Company, 2 pages Grosscurth, Adam, 2 pages Von Grosse, Aristid, 1 page Guggenheim Foundation (H. A. Moe), 2 pages Gunn, Ross (Naval Research Laboratory), 2 pages Gushee, Vera, 5 pages (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - H, 1932, Hale, G. E., 17 pages Hale, William B, 3 pages Hall, W. J., 2 pages Halpern, Joseph L., 7 pages Halstead, F. A., 2 pages Hamilton Beach Company, 1 page Hancock and Pence, 1 page Harrell, B. L., 3 pages Harris Brothers Company, 5 pages Hartmann, J., (La Plata), 1 page Harvard College Observatory (Shapley), 1 page Hass, Edward, 2 pages Hayward, K., 2 pages Heck, Charles M., 3 pages Heinrich, W. W., 1 page Helbronner, Paul, 2 pages Hillebrand, Wilma Jean, 2 pages Hillsdale College (E. B. Penrod), 2 pages Hix, John, 1 page Hobart, Frank G., 2 pages Hogness, F. R., 4 pages Hohn, S. (Lick), 1 page Horicon, Wisconsin (L. A. Plantz), 2 pages Hotton, J. S., 2 pages Howards, Burton E., 1 page Hoyt, Martha (Brashear Secretary), 3 pages Hubble, Edwin (Mount Wilson), 3 pages Huffer, R. C., 2 pages Hyde, J. E., 1 page Hynek, J. Allen, 11 pages (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - I-J, 1932, Ilford, Limited, 2 pages Industrial Power, 1 page Institution of International Education, 5 pages New Inventions and Patents Magazine, 1 page Iowa State College (William Kunerth), 2 pages Ivor Nicholson and Watsons, Limited, 2 pages International Astronomical Union, 23 pages D. O. James Manufacturing Company, 2 pages James, Bob, 1 page Johns Hopkins (R. W. Wood), 1 page Johnson, Alfred, 2 pages Spencer, Jones, 1 page Jorgensen, Mrs. Jergen, 1 page Julia, Sr. M., 1 page Junior Home, 2 pages (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - K-L, 1932, Kamensky, George, 3 pages Kane, Lucille, 1 page Kantro Glass Company, 1 page Keadlers Jewlry Store, 2 pages Kearney and Trecker, 2 pages Keener, Joe, 1 page Kendallville Foundry, 5 pages Kennedy, Mrs. E. B., 2 pages Kincaid, Harrison, 1 page Kipp and Zonen, 4 pages Klumak, Robert, 2 pages Kodaikanal Observatory, 2 pages Kohl, Otto, 12 pages Kovalendo, Micheal S., 2 pages Kremers, Roland E., 3 pages Krieger, C. J., 6 pages La Plata Observatory (J. Hartmann), 3 pages Lawton, Harry, 5 pages Lee, Edna F., 5 pages Lee, Oliver J. (Northwestern), 13 pages Leeds and Northrup Company, 5 pages Lemon, Harvey B., 4 pages Lick Observatory, (R. G. Aitken), 5 pages Lindblad, Bertil, 2 pages Lobdell, H. E. (MIT), 1 page London Guarantee and Accident Company, 4 pages Lougee, Arthur, 1 page Robert Lundin, Incorporated, 2 pages Lundmark, Knut, 3 pages Lutz, G. H., 4 pages Luyten, W. J., 2 pages (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - M, 1932, McCormick, Harold F., 3 pages McGill University (A. S. Eve), 2 pages McMaster-Carr Supply Company, 1 page McMillan, W. D., 28 pages Madison, Auto License Division, 1 page Mandel Brothers, 1 page Manville, Mahlon, 1 page Marchant Calculating Machine Company, 3 pages Markovitz, William, 12 pages Marshall, Roy, 2 pages Peter L. Martin, 1 page Mayer, Milton S., 1 page Mechanical Specialties, 1 page Thomas R. Meehan Company, 1 page Mees, C. E. K. (Eastman Kodak), 3 pages Mehlin, Theodore, G., 1 page Merrill, John E., 2 pages Merrill, Paul W., 11 pages Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, 2 pages Mikhalsky, N., 4 pages Miller, Dayton C., 1 page Milwaukee Machinery Company, 1 page Minerva, 1 page Minneapolis Public Library, 2 pages Mitchell, S. A. (Leander McCormick Observatory), 14 pages Moffitt, G. W., 4 pages Moffitt, Wilbur, 1 page Mohler, Orren, 2 pages Monk, G. S., 2 pages Montgomery Ward, 6 pages Morehouse, D. W. (Drake University), 9 pages Moulton, J. R., 2 pages Mount Wilson Observatory, 1 page (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - N, 1932, Natal Museum, Pietermaritzburg, 1 page National Academy of Science, 12 pages National Advisory Council on Radio in Education, 1 page National Research Council, 3 reports, 43 pages Naval Observatory (Sunspot Reports), 39 pages New York Times, 2 pages Newton, H. W. (Greenwich), 4 pages Ivor Nicholson and Watson, 1 page Norman and Willetts, 1 page Numerov, B. V., 4 pages (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - O-Q, 1932, Ognodnikoff, K., 1 page Oort, J. H., 1 page Opferkuch, K., 2 pages Peterson, Max, 15 pages Pettit, Edison, 3 pages Phoenix Caster Company, 1 page Physikalische Zeitschrift, 1 page Pillars, Helen, 2 pages Plaskett, J. S. (Dominion Astrophysical Observatory), 4 pages Pogo, A, 3 pages Popular Astronomy (C. H. Ginrich), 3 pages Popular Mechanics, 1 page Porter, H. H., 5 pages Post Office, Williams Bay, 2 pages Post Office, Milwaukee, 1 page Postal Telegraph Cable Company, 2 pages Pyle, W. R., 4 pages (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Perkins Project, 150 pages, 1932 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Questions answered, 1932 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - R, 1932, Radio Arts Productions, 1 page Randall, C. E., 2 pages Recht, A. W., 8 pages Remington Rand, 9 pages Ritchie, Mary, 5 pages Roach, Franklin, 3 pages C. A. Roberts Co., 7 pages Rodes, Franklin, 1 page Romare, Ethel, 1 page Ross, Clarence, 2 pages Ross, F. E., 5 pages Rothschild, James B., 1 page Royal Astronomical Society (tour), 18 pages Rydnick, Paul, 5 pages LaRuelle, E. A. D., 2 pages Rufus, W. Carl, 2 pages Rumford Fund, 3 pages Russell, H. N., 1 page Rybka, E., 2 pages Requests, 2 pages (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - S, 1932, Sabine, Paul E., 2 pages Sanborn, H. D., 1 page Schilt, Jan (Columbia), 3 pages Schlesinger, Frank (Yale), 1 page Schwarzman, Marguerite E., 2 pages Schwede, Harold F., 2 pages Science Service, 6 pages Seares, F. H. (Mount Wilson), 7 pages Sears, Roebuck and Company, 6 pages Segal Machinery Company, 3 pages Shaw, Walden W., 3 pages Sheldon, Paul S., 2 pages Simpson, Wesley, 2 pages Slaught, H. E. (University of Chicago), 3 pages Snodgrass, G. M., 1 page Spencer Lens Company, 2 pages Squier, Major George O., 2 pages State Entomologist, 1 page Stebbins, Joel (University of Wisconsin), 10 pages Stetson, Harlan (Perkins), 7 pages Stokley, James (Franklin Institute), 2 pages Stonyhurst College Observatory, 1 page Struve, Otto, 1 page Stuart, Eunice, 1 page Studebaker Sales Corporation, 3 pages Sullivan, F. R., 2 pages Swasey, Ambrose, 3 pages Kungliga Vetenskapsakademien Bibliothek, Sweden, 5 pages Swings, P., 10 pages (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - S-T, 1932, Shapley, Harlow, 37 pages Takamine, T., 5 pages Tallmadge, T. E., 3 pages Taylor, H. O. (Wheaton College), 6 pages University of Texas, Office of the President, 2 pages Thermal Syndicate, Incorporated, 2 pages Tokyo Astronomical Observatory (Y. Fujita), 2 pages (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Requests for slide catalogs, 1932 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - U, 1932, Unsold, Albrecht (Kiel), 13 pages United States Geological Survey, 1 page United States Naval Observatory, 1 page University of Chicago Bookstore (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1932 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1932 (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
  - U, 1932, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, electric bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, mowing bills University of Chicago Business Manager (L. R. Steere) (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - U, 1932, University of Chicago Bursar University of Chicago Cashier University of Chicago Comptroller, petty statements (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - U, 1932, University of Chicago Comptroller, payroll University of Chicago Divisional Dean (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - U, 1932, University of Chicago graduate students reports (Dean Gale) University of Chicago Dean Gale, personal University of Chicago Library (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - U, 1932, University of Chicago University of Chicago President’s Office (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - University of Chicago Press, 1932 (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - U, 1932, University of Chicago Press, Epsilon Aurigae University of Chicago Publicity Office (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - University of Chicago payroll, 1932 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - U-V, 1932, University of Chicago Purchasing Agent University of Chicago Recorder University of Chicago Board of Trustees (J. M. Stiffler) University of Chicago Vice President’s Office, 1 page Vanderbilt University Library, 1 page Van Arnam, Ralph N., 2 pages Van Biesbroeck, G., 2 pages Van Biesbroeck, Simone, 1 page Vierteljahschrift, 2 pages Vonderweid, E. de, 1 page (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - W-Z, 1932, Walworth Times, 3 pages Warner and Swasey Company, 20 pages Washburne, C. W., 3 pages Washington, George (birthday), 1 page Washington, Lawrence D., 2 pages Waska, J. A., 1 page Watanabe, Y. (United States Bureau of Immigration), 1 page United States Weather Bureau, Chicago, 1 page United States Weather Bureau, Milwaukee, 1 page Westburg Engineering Company, 3 pages Weston Electric Company, 2 pages Wheaton College (H. O. Taylor), 2 pages Norman-Willetts Company, 1 page Williams Bay Post Office (C. A. Waterbury), 6 pages University of Wisconsin Department of Economic Entomology, 1 page Wolf, Max, 3 pages Wood, Evan J. (Alpine, Texas), 1 page Wood, Fred W., 2 pages Woodmanse Manufacturing Company, 1 page Wrigley, William Jr., 4 pages Wylie, C. C. (University of Iowa), 9 pages YMCA, 9 pages Yale University, 1 page Yamamoto, Issei, 5 pages Yerkes Observatory, 1 page Young A., 1 page Carl Zeiss, Incorporated, 3 pages (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Visitors, 1932 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Weather reports, 1932, Summer students’ reports, 8 pages Notices, 16 pages Yerkes staff reports, 5 pages Requisitions Century of Progress newsletters, 5 pages (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Reports for American Astrological Society, 1933 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - A, 1933, Demonstrations, 2 pages Abastumani, George USSR, 1 page Abbot, C. G. (Smithsonian), 2 pages Adams, Walter S. (Mount Wilson), 8 pages Agfa Ansco Corporation, 8 pages United States Department of Agriculture, 1 page Aitken, R. G. (Lick), 10 pages Albrecht, Sebastian (Dudley), 26 pages Alter, Dinsmore, 5 pages American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Rumford Fund Committee, 56 pages American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1 page American Astrological Society (Raymond S. Dugan), 7 pages American Council on Education, 5 pages American Express Company, 2 pages American Philosophical Society, 1 page American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1 page Anding, Dr. (Gotha), 1 page Armenter, F., 2 pages Associated Press, 8 pages Astill, A. St., 2 pages Astronomical Journal, 1 page Astronomical Society of the Pacific, 4 pages Astronomisches Buro Wien, 3 pages Automatic File and Index Company, 2 pages d’Azambuga, M., 2 pages (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Applications for positions, 1933 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - B, 1933, Bank deposits Balmer, H. F., 2 pages Barnard, R. W., (University of Chicago), 1 page Barrett, S. A. (Milwaukee Public Museum), 3 pages Bastin, E. S. (University of Chicago), 9 pages Bausch and Lomb, 5 pages Beck, Charlton T. (University of Chicago Alumni Council), 1 page Becker, Wilhelm, 1 page Belgique Observatory Royal, 1 page Bell and Howell, 2 pages Beloit College, 1 page Charles H. Besly Company, 7 pages E. A. Bishop, Publisher (postcards), 4 pages Bobrovnikoff, N. T. (Perkins), 6 pages Bodine Electric Company, 6 pages Box, B. J., 4 pages Boothroyd, S. L. (Cornell), 7 pages Borka, A., 4 pages Boss, Benjamin (Dudley), 1 page Bowie, William (United States Coast and Geodetic), 2 pages Braniff Arilines, 1 page Brooklyn College, 2 pages Brown, E. V. L., 2 pages ten Bruggencate, P., 2 pages Bryce, Allan, 1 page Burlington Brass Foundry, 2 pages Burns, Garm J., 1 page Burson, V., 1 page Buttles, L. I., 3 pages (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - C, 1933, Calhoun, Evelyn, 1 page Cambridge Instrument Company, 1 page Cannon, Annie J., 2 pages Carroll, J. A. (University of Aberdeen), 3 pages Catalana, M. A., 1 page Cattell, J. M., 2 pages Celebrated Players Film Corporation, 1 page Chicago Camera Club, 4 pages B.W. Christian and Company, 3 pages Christmas greetings, 5 pages University of Cincinnati, 1 page Claridge, George C., 3 pages Compton, A. H. (University of Chicago), 3 pages Comrie, L. J., 14 pages Copelin, 1 page Corbly, L. J., 1 page Cornell, Herbert W., 2 pages Corning Glass Works, 4 pages Cory, Ralph (Royal Institute), 1 page Couder, A., 2 pages Cranz, R. A. F., 2 pages Cream City Scale Company, 7 pages Crommelin, A. C. D., 3 pages Charles A. Crowell Company, 1 page Crump, Clifford, 3 pages Curtis, H. D., 1 pages Custer, H. B., 5 pages Customs Service, Milwaukee, 1 page (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Century of Progress, Arcturus, 130 pages, 1933 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - D, 1933, Davis, Watson (Science Newsletter), 1 page Deutsches Museum (C. H. Fuchs), 6 pages Dickerson, J. S. (University of Chicago records), 13 pages Dewitt, J. H., 7 pages Dietzgen Company, 1 page R. R. Donnelley Company, 2 pages Dugan, R. S. (American Astronomical Society, Princeton), 13 pages Dunham, Theodore (Mount Wilson), 10 pages (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - E, 1933, Eames, Claude, 1 page Eastman Kodak Company, 92 pages Eklund, Helen B., 2 pages Elmer, C. W., 1 page Emanuelli, Pio (Vatican), 7 pages Eclipse 1934, 2 pages (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - F-G, 1933, Falconer, D. P., 1 page Farnsworth, G., 2 pages J. W. Fecker Company, 10 pages First National Bank, 3 pages Fish-Schurman Corporation, 4 pages Foote, H. M., 5 pages Forsythe, W. E. (General Electric), 4 pages Fox, Phillip (Adler), 26 pages Freeport, Illinois (Hoeffer, C. A.), 2 pages Frost, S. E. Jr., 4 pages Furness, Caroline E., 1 page Gaertner Scientific Corporation, 12 pages General Transparency Displays, 2 pages Gevaert Company, 7 pages Gibbs, R. C., 1 page Gingrich, C. H. (Popular Astronomy), 17 pages Gleissberg, Wolfgang, 2 pages C. P. Goerz Company, 1 page Governor’s Office, Wisconsin, 1 page Green, Warren K. (Amherst), 2 pages Grutzner, F. P., (American Society of Mechanical Engineers), 5 pages Guggenheim Foundation, (H. A. Moe), 5 pages (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - H-J, 1933, Hale, George E., 2 pages Halpern, J. L., 13 pages Harding, A. M., 4 pages Hargrove, W. C., 2 pages Harvard College Observatory, 2 pages Haverford College Library, 2 pages Hawes, M. A., 3 pages Heinrich, W. W. (Prague), 14 pages Helmholz, H. F., 2 pages Hertzsprung, E., 6 pages Gustav Heyde, 1 page Adam Hilger Limited, 5 pages Hogness, T. R. (University of Chicago), 8 pages Holzer, Purl E., 3 pages Horder’s, 2 pages Howard, C. A., 1 page Howard, Frank B., 2 pages Huffer C. M. (Washburn), 8 pages Huffer, R. C. (Beloit), 9 pages Hungarian National Observatory Budapest, 5 pages Ilford Limited, 1 page Iljinsky, I. I. (Kiev), 2 pages Institute de France, 1 page Iyer, P. R. Chidambara, 2 pages Jacobsen T. S., 3 pages Jahn and Olliver, 1 page Jensen, J. C., 2 pages Jessup, M. K., 3 pages Johnson, Elise E., 1 page Johnson Heat Regulating Company, 1 page Journal of the Optical Society of America, 1 page Joy, Alfred H., 1 page Justin, E. M., 1 page Finding Chart, 1 page (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - K-L, 1933, Keller, Ernest G., 2 pages Kendallville Foundry, 3 pages Kennan, P. C., 1 page Killian, J., 1 page Kiwanis Club, Elkhorn, 1 page Klingaman, William, 1 page Kobold, H. (Astronomische Nachrichten), 6 pages Kodaikanal Observatory, 3 pages Kohl, Otto, 5 pages Kopff, A., 2 pages Krieger, C. J. (St. Louis University), 30 pages Kropp Company, 1 page Laing, G. J. (University of Chicago Press), 6 pages Lause, J., 3 pages Lemaitre, A., 1 page Lemon, H. B. (University of Chicago), 4 pages Leningrad Scientific Research Institute, 1 page Leonids, 4 pages Leppert, R. E., 1 page Leuschner, A. O. (University of Colorado), 4 pages Levinson, Horace, 1 page Liebermann, E., 1 page Linton, Edgar, 3 pages Lohmann, E., 2 pages London Guarantee and Accident Company, 1 page Loria, R. O., 1 page Lundmark, Knut, 5 pages (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - M, 1933, McCarthy, Edward L., 1 page McCarthy, Oscar W., 1 page McCuskey, Sid, 4 pages McLeod, Noah W., 5 pages MacMillan, W. D. (University of Chicago), 5 pages McNally, R. E. (YMCA), 2 pages Marchant Calculating Company, 1 page Instituto y Observatorio, Marina, 1 page Markov, A. (Leningrad), 4 pages Markowitz, William, 17 pages Martz, Edwin P. Jr., 7 pages Mees, C. C. K. (Eastman Kodak), 9 pages Meinhardt, Albert, 2 pages Men’s Community Club, Williams Bay, 2 pages Menzel, William, E., 2 pages Merrill, Paul W., (Mount Wilson), 6 pages Metal Specialties Manufacturing Company, 1 page Miczaika, G. R., 1 page Miller, Freeman D., 1 page Milwaukee Astronomical Society, 1 page University of Mississippi Library, 2 pages Mitchell, Maude, 2 pages Modern Coal Burner Company, 1 page Monk, G. S. (University of Chicago), 11 pages Monnig, Oscar E., 3 pages Montgomery Ward and Company, 4 pages Moore, Charlotte E., 5 pages Moore, W. L., 2 pages Morehouse, D. W. (Drake University), 1 page Morelock, H. W., 3 pages Morschhauser, W. A., 1 page Mortensen, H. J., 2 pages Moscow University, 3 pages Municipal Airport, Chicago, 1 page (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - N-P, 1933, Natal Museum, 1 page National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council, 47 pages United States Naval Observatory, 2 pages Nelson, James F., 1 page New York Times, 4 pages Norman-Willets Company, 1 page Northwestern Military Academy, 1 page Notsuki, M., 4 pages Numerov, B. V., 1 page Oxford University Press, 1 page Palmer, Charles K., 2 pages Parker, Mrs. Norman, 3 pages Parkinson, M. W. (University of Chicago Press), 1 page Pathe News, 1 page Pawling, Jesse, 1 page Payne, Cecilia, 8 pages Pease, F. G. (Mount Wilson), 7 pages Peters, H. J., 2 pages Pettit, Edison (Mount Wilson), 20 pages Physical Review, 2 pages Plaskett, J. S., 1 page Plecher, Andrew, 2 pages Pogo, Alexander, 10 pages Popular Astronomy, 9 pages Porter, H. H., 5 pages Post Office, Washington, 1 page Post Office, Williams Bay, 2 pages Presse Photo G.M.B.H., 3 pages Bureau of Publications, Washington, DC, 4 pages Pyle, Alfred J., 2 pages (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Perkins Project, 230 pages, 1933 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - P-Q, 1933, Photographic Supply Department Inquiries Questions Answered (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - R, 1933, Rawlings, J. A. (Associated Press), 2 pages Reaves, S. W., 1 page Recht, A. W., 5 pages Reglin, G., 5 pages Remington Rand, 2 pages Richtyner, F. K. (Journal of the Optical Society of America), 6 pages Ripley, Mr., 1 page Ritchey, G. W. (United States Naval Observatory), 3 pages Robertson, H. P. 1 page Rodes, Luis, 1 page Ross, F. E., 12 pages Rosseland, S., 1 page Rosenberg, 2 pages Royds, R. T. (Kodaikanal Observatory) 3 pages Rudnick, P., 1 page Rufus, W. Carl, 2 pages Russell, H. N. (Princeton), 18 pages (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - S, 1933, St. Louis Post Dispatch, 1 page San Fernando Observatory, 1 page Schlesinger, Frank (Yale), 10 pages Schlesinger, H. I. (University of Chicago), 1 page Science Press, 1 page Science Service, 1 page Scientia, 6 pages Scientific American, 4 pages Scientific Monthly, 3 pages Sears Roebuck and Company, 2 pages Severinski, N., 1 page Sibley, Ru Ray, 4 pages Simonov, Gleb V., 6 pages Smith, Elliott, 4 pages Societe Royale des Sciences de Liege, 2 pages Sola, J. Comas, 2 pages Soper, Edmund D. (Ohio Wesleyan University), 14 pages Sparks, Brian, 3 pages Sparks, William S., 2 pages Stager, W., 1 page Bureau of Standards, 1 page Stebbins, Joel (Washburn Observatory), 3 pages Steins, K., 1 page Stetson, Harlan T., 15 pages Stevens Hotel, 1 page Stewart, Charles D., 2 pages Stifler, James M. (University of Chicago Board of Trustees), 2 pages Stracke, G., 4 pages Street, Mrs., 2 pages Stromgren, E., 16 pages Strull, Charles, 11 pages Struve, George, 1 page Sutcliffe, J. E., 3 pages Swartz, Henrietta, 7 pages Swings, P., (Liege) 9 pages Synchronome, W., 1 page (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Shapey, 53 pages, 1933 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - T-U, 1933, Tass, A., 2 pages Taylor, H. O., 1 page Taylor, Philip, 2 pages Thompson, R. E., 2 pages Time Magazine, 1 page Tomkins, T. K., 4 pages Tulane, Axel, 1 page Twyman, F. (Adam Hilger), 3 pages Tyrell, F. J., 5 pages University of Chicago Bursar (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1933 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, 1933 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, houses, 1933 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - U, 1933, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, light and power bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, Business Manager University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, water and sewer (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - U, 1933, University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, mowing bills University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, R. E. Doty’s memoranda University of Chicago Buildings and Grounds, coal (Box 146, Folder 4)